Krushnasinh Jadeja

Experienced Fullstack Developer having 5+ years in development. My key role is to build a career as an efficient person in any field, which will give me as opportunity to work on challenging problems. Its my duty to make development of myself and increase the growth of organization.

kdjadeja209@gmail.com



Rajkot, Gujarat



🛱 linktr.ee/krushnasinh



in linkedin.com/in/krushnasinh-jadeja-a02017126

WORK EXPERIENCE

Associate Team Leader Simform Solutions LLP

01/2023 - Present

Work

- As an Associate Team Leader. I oversee a team of 20 members. coordinating efforts to develop tailored software architectures that meet our clients' specific requirements.
- Collaborating closely with clients, I ensure a thorough understanding of their needs, facilitating effective communication and project management throughout the development lifecycle.
- My primary focus is on delivering solutions that align precisely with client expectations, leveraging efficient workflows and proactive problem-solving to achieve successful outcomes.

Software Engineer Simform Solutions LLP

06/2021 - 01/2023

- Working as a MERN stack developer. I have implemented many web portal which is mostly built in ReactJS and NodeJS
- Responsible for development and delivery of the complete frontend of products like IP based cloud solution and Nodejs application which helps users to achieve goals...
- Developed several quickweb apps within short timelinesfor multiple client requirements.

Software Engineer

Wings Tech Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

03/2020 - 05/2021

Work

- Worked as a Fullstack developer. I have implemented many web portal which is mostly built in ReactJS and NodeJS.
- Being a small tight-knit team,I got a chance to wear many hats,from requirement analysis to generating the build.

Web Developer

Emipro Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

04/2019 - 01/2020

 I worked as a Web Developer. I have implemented Amazon odoo connector app.

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, **Computer Engineering**

Marwadi University

2017 - 2019

CPI 8.20 (Out of 10)

SKILLS



PROJECTS

Database Monitoring Web Application

- Database performance monitoring for the Data Platform, with fast root cause analysis and visibility across the Microsoft data estate.
- At-a-glance view of database environment health. Storage forecasting powered by predictive analytics. Identify contributing problems in the OS and virtual environment.
- Proactive alerting and response system. Find and fix high-impact queries.
- Tech Stack: ReactJS, GraphQL, Jest, Typescript, .NET, Azure.

Online Training Platform

- It is an online platform that enables US police personnel to get trained in different programs. Within the platform, the admin adds the trainees. Trainees can view different programs listed that are locked. On completing each program other sessions get unlocked.
- They can view their performance in the training program. Trainees can attend the sessions which are free and paid ones, for the paid ones they can select the program and complete the payment process. Admin can view the programs the trainees have completed and undergoing, view analytic
- Tech Stack: ReactJS, Redux, NodeJS, Express, Azure

Social Media Platform

- It is an application that enables users to connect with other users and ask for help when they are in danger. Users can register themselves, connect with other users, like/comment/share other users' posts, upload posts.
- Users can exchange text messages with each other. On being in a dangerous position, user can ask for help that enables alert notification to other users in the proximity who are using the application.
- Tech Stack: NodeJS, Express, Twillio, AWS

Online Workout Platform

- It is a subscription base workout App. In this app admin can upload the workout videos and user will get that videos and also push notifications for that new workout as well.
- Some features include Workout videos, new workout push notifications, complete workout trackers, Save your workouts for later, set a weekly goal, Weight Tracker and many more.
- Tech Stack: NodeJS, Express, AWS.

E-Commerce Platform

- A marketplace platform that facilitates merchants to connect with huvers for their products. Merchants can register and upload their products with their details, and images. Each merchant can manage their orders and payment transactions within the platform.
- Buyers can browse products from different categories, and merchants, add products from multiple merchants to the cart, complete the payment online, and many more.
- Tech Stack: ReactJS, Typescript, Redux, AWS.